http://www.vhbio.com/privacy-policy/

ImmunologyMolecular BiologyTransplant Diagnostics
Antibodies for Flow CytometryAntibodies for HumanAntibodies for MouseAntibodies for RatCell LinesCell Separation MediaComplement Dependent Cytotoxicity TestingComplement ProteinsImmune Cell EnrichmentNeuroscience ReagentsParoxysmal Nocturnal Haemoglobinuria (PNH) ScreeningArmoured ReagentsMolecular DiagnosticsMolecular MicrobiologyNext-Generation SequencingPCR Reagents Plastics and AccessoriesSample Preparation and ProcessingSanger SequencingAntibody DetectionInstruments and softwareMolecular TypingSerological Typing
Abeta AntibodiesCD AntibodiesGold Conjugted AntibodiesHaemostasis AntibodiesMisc AntibodiesSNARE Complex AntibodiesCD AntibodiesCell AntibodiesCell Signalling AntibodiesGold Conjugated AntibodiesMHC Antibodies (Class I)MHC Antibodies (Class II)TCR AntibodiesCD AntibodiesGold Conjugated AntibodiesTCR AntibodiesAdult Mouse POMC / GFPBovine Trabecular MeshworkCardiac EndothelialHippocampalHuman Cerebral Microvascular EndothelialHuman Smooth MuscleHypothalamicMotor NeuronOligodendrocyticOvarianPituitaryIsolation of Viable Human Lymphocytes from Peripheral BloodIsolation of Viable Human Polymorphonuclear CellsIsolation of Viable Lymphocytes from Peripheral Blood of Mammalian SpeciesIsolation of Viable Mouse Lymphocytes from Lymphoid TissueIsolation of Viable Pancreatic Islet CellsIsolation of Viable Rabbit Lymphocytes from Lymphoid TissueIsolation of Viable Rat Lymphocytes from Lymphoid TissueCytotoxicity MediaGuinea Pig ComplementHuman ComplementOther ComplementRabbit ComplementHuman Cell Purification ImmunocolumnsMouse Cell Purification ImmunocolumnsRat Cell Purification ImmunocolumnsELISA KitsNerve Growth FactorSARS-CoV-2Clinical MicrobiologyMolecular GeneticsMolecular OncologyDNA-Free PCR Reagents and Assays for Pathogen DetectionPathogen DNA IsolationTarget CaptureEnd-Point PCRPCR Plastics and ConsumablesqPCR MastermixesAutomated Nucleic Acid ExtractionBacterial Genomic DNA IsolationPCR PurificationPrecipiation ReagentsSample Collection, Transport and ProcessingCapillary RegenerationConformational AnalysisCycle Sequencing KitsDye Terminator RemovalFormamideRunning BufferSequencing PolymersAdvanced Crossmatch testingComplement Binding HLA Antibody IdentificationELISA-Based HLA Antibody IdentificationFlow Cytometry Based HLA Antibody IdentificationLuminex-based HLA Antibody IdentificationNon-HLA Luminex Based Antibody IdentificationSerological-based HLA antibody identificationAutomated Pipettors and DispensorsNGS InstrumentationReaders and analysersSoftwareNext Generation SequencingNon-HLA GenotypingReal-Time PCR TypingReverse Sequence-Specific Oligonucleotide TypingSequence Based TypingSequence-Specific Primer TypingHLA Tissue Typing TraysMonoclonal TraysSerological Ancillary ProductsSerological Reagents
Adult Mouse GnRH/GFP Cell LineAdult Mouse HypothalamicAdult Mouse Kiss/GFP Cell LinesAdult Mouse NPY/GFP Cell LineEmbryonic Mouse HypothalamicEmbryonic Rat HypothalamicBaby rabbit complementLow Toxicity Rabbit ComplementRabbit Complement for use with Human LymphocytesRabbit Complement for use with Human Peripheral Blood LymphocytesAntibodies to Nerve Growth FactorUltrapure Nerve Growth FactorAutomated Pathogen DiagnosisRoutine Molecular Pathogen DiagnosisC9orf72 PCR/CEDMPK PCR/CEFMR1 ControlsFMR1 mPCRFMR1 PCR/CEHTT PCR/CESMN1 PCR/CESMN1/2 PCR/CETOMM40 PCR/CEBCR-ABL1 Monitoring | Major Fusion TranscriptsBCR-ABL1 Monitoring | Minor Fusion TranscriptsTargeted NGS Panels | Lung CancerTargeted NGS Panels | Pan-CancerAncillary Products for PCR Pathogen DetectionDNA-Free PCR Mastermixes for Pathogen DetectionDNA-Free Taq Ploymerases for Pathogen DetectionEnrichment and Isolation of Microbial DNAMicrobiome EnrichmentClinical ExomePan-CancerPharmacogeneticsDNA PolymerasesNucleotidesPCR MastermixesOther Plastics and ConsumablesPCR PlatesPlate Sealers and CapsAutomated Large Sample Volume Nucleic Acid ExtractionAutomated Routine Nucleic Acid Extraction384-well plate kits96-well plate kitsColumn KitsEnzymatic PCR PurificationResinsPathogenic Sample Collection KitTransport MediaOptima DTRParamagnetic BeadsPerforma DTRPurification KitsLambda Antigen TrayLambda Antigen Tray MixedLambda Antigen Tray Single AntigenFlowPRA Ancillary ProductsFlowPRA ScreeningFlowPRA Single AntigenFlowPRA SpecificLABScreen Ancillary ReagentsLABScreen MICALABScreen MixedLABScreen MultiLABScreen PRALABScreen Single AntigenLABScreen Single Antigen SupplementLinkSeq VIAFLO ASSIST Liquid Handler KitIon Chef SystemIon GeneStudio S5 Sequencing SystemsLABScan 3DTypeStream Visual NGS Analysis SoftwareAllType FASTplex NGSAllType NGSAllType NGS Ancillary ProductsCytokine GenotypingHNA GenotypingKIR SSO GenotypingKIR SSP GenotypingABO Typing KitsAccessoriesHLA Specific Typing KitsHLA Typing KitsHPA Typing KitsKIR Typing KitsLABType Ancillary ReagentsLABType SSOLABType XR and CWDTray Aspirator LTSeCore GSSPSeCore SBTAllSet Gold SSP DNA Wipe TestAllSet Gold SSP High ResolutionAllSet Gold SSP Low ResolutionMicro SSP 96-well transfer deviceMicro SSP Allele Specific TraysMicro SSP AmbistripsMicro SSP Ancillary ProductsMicro SSP Bulk Primer SetsMicro SSP Generic TraysMicro SSP High Resolution TraysTerasaki HLA Tissue Typing TraysTerasaki Supplement HLA Tissue Typing TraysTerasaki Cover SlidesTerasaki TraysB27 Monoclonal AntibodyBulk Monoclonal AntibodiesCytotoxic ControlsDynabeadsFluoroBeads Isolation ReagentsFluoroQuench Staining/Quenching ReagentGoat IgG Anti-Human KappaHeavy Mineral OilLympho-KwikPooled Human SerumRabbit Complement
AsuragenCedarlaneCelemicsEdge BiosystemsEKF DiagnosticsMolzymOne LambdaPSSRovalabVH Bio
Armoured ReagentsMolecular GeneticsMolecular OncologyAntibodies for Flow CytometryAntibodies for HumanAntibodies for MouseAntibodies for RatCell LinesCell Separation MediaComplement Dependent Cytotoxicity TestingComplement ProteinsImmune Cell EnrichmentNeuroscience ReagentsParoxysmal Nocturnal Haemoglobinuria (PNH) ScreeningNext-Generation SequencingPCR PurificationPlastics Consumables and AccessoriesSample PreparationSanger SequencingSequencing BuffersSample Collection, Transport and ProcessingDNA-Free PCR Reagents and Assays for Pathogen DetectionMolecular Diagnostics for Clinical MicrobiologyPathogen DNA IsolationStandard PCR ReagentsAntibody DetectionInstruments and softwareMolecular TypingSerological TypingAutomated Large Sample Volume Nucleic Acid ExtractionAutomated Routine Nucleic Acid ExtractionEnd-Point PCRqPCR Mastermixes
SARS-CoV-2C9orf72 PCR/CEDMPK PCR/CEFMR1 ControlsFMR1 mPCRFMR1 PCR/CEHTT PCR/CESMN1 PCR/CESMN1/2 PCR/CETOMM40 PCR/CEBCR-ABL1 Monitoring | Major Fusion TranscriptsBCR-ABL1 Monitoring | Minor Fusion TranscriptsTargeted NGS Panels | Lung CancerTargeted NGS Panels | Pan-CancerAbeta AntibodiesCD AntibodiesGold Conjugted AntibodiesHaemostasis AntibodiesMisc AntibodiesSNARE Complex AntibodiesCD AntibodiesCell AntibodiesCell Signalling AntibodiesGold Conjugated AntibodiesMHC Antibodies (Class I)MHC Antibodies (Class II)TCR AntibodiesCD AntibodiesGold Conjugated AntibodiesTCR AntibodiesAdult Mouse POMC / GFPBovine Trabecular MeshworkCardiac EndothelialHippocampalHuman Cerebral Microvascular EndothelialHuman Smooth MuscleHypothalamicMotor NeuronOligodendrocyticOvarianPituitaryIsolation of Viable Human Lymphocytes from Peripheral BloodIsolation of Viable Human Polymorphonuclear CellsIsolation of Viable Lymphocytes from Peripheral Blood of Mammalian SpeciesIsolation of Viable Mouse Lymphocytes from Lymphoid TissueIsolation of Viable Pancreatic Islet CellsIsolation of Viable Rabbit Lymphocytes from Lymphoid TissueIsolation of Viable Rat Lymphocytes from Lymphoid TissueCytotoxicity MediaGuinea Pig ComplementHuman ComplementOther ComplementRabbit ComplementHuman Cell Purification ImmunocolumnsMouse Cell Purification ImmunocolumnsRat Cell Purification ImmunocolumnsELISA KitsNerve Growth FactorTarget Capture384-well plate kits96-well plate kitsColumn KitsEnzymatic PCR PurificationResinsBacterial Genomic DNA IsolationPrecipiation ReagentsCapillary RegenerationConformational AnalysisCycle Sequencing KitsDye Terminator RemovalFormamideRunning BufferSequencing PolymersPathogenic Sample Collection KitTransport MediaAncillary Products for PCR Pathogen DetectionDNA-Free PCR Mastermixes for Pathogen DetectionDNA-Free Taq Ploymerases for Pathogen DetectionAutomationRoutine Molecular Pathogen DiagnosisEnrichment and Isolation of Microbial DNAMicrobiome EnrichmentAdvanced Crossmatch testingComplement Binding HLA Antibody IdentificationELISA-Based HLA Antibody IdentificationFlow Cytometry Based HLA Antibody IdentificationLuminex-based HLA Antibody IdentificationNon-HLA Luminex Based Antibody IdentificationSerological-based HLA antibody identificationAutomated Pipettors and DispensorsNGS InstrumentationReaders and analysersSoftwareNext Generation SequencingNon-HLA GenotypingReal-Time PCR TypingReverse Sequence-Specific Oligonucleotide TypingSequence Based TypingSequence-Specific Primer TypingHLA Tissue Typing TraysMonoclonal TraysSerological Ancillary ProductsSerological ReagentsDNA PolymerasesNucleotidesPCR Mastermixes
Adult Mouse GnRH/GFP Cell LineAdult Mouse HypothalamicAdult Mouse Kiss/GFP Cell LinesAdult Mouse NPY/GFP Cell LineEmbryonic Mouse HypothalamicEmbryonic Rat HypothalamicBaby rabbit complementLow Toxicity Rabbit ComplementRabbit Complement for use with Human LymphocytesRabbit Complement for use with Human Peripheral Blood LymphocytesAntibodies to Nerve Growth FactorUltrapure Nerve Growth FactorClinical ExomePan-CancerPharmacogeneticsOptima DTRParamagnetic BeadsPerforma DTRPurification KitsAutomated enrichment and isolation of microbial DNAAutomated Pathogen DNA Isolation and broad-range PCR/Real-Time PCR AnalysisInstrumentationLambda Antigen TrayLambda Antigen Tray MixedLambda Antigen Tray Single AntigenFlowPRA Ancillary ProductsFlowPRA ScreeningFlowPRA Single AntigenFlowPRA SpecificLABScreen Ancillary ReagentsLABScreen MICALABScreen MixedLABScreen MultiLABScreen PRALABScreen Single AntigenLABScreen Single Antigen SupplementLinkSeq VIAFLO ASSIST Liquid Handler KitIon Chef SystemIon GeneStudio S5 Sequencing SystemsLABScan 3DTypeStream Visual NGS Analysis SoftwareAllType FASTplex NGSAllType NGSAllType NGS Ancillary ProductsCytokine GenotypingHNA GenotypingKIR SSO GenotypingKIR SSP GenotypingABO Typing KitsAccessoriesHLA Specific Typing KitsHLA Typing KitsHPA Typing KitsKIR Typing KitsLABType Ancillary ReagentsLABType SSOLABType XR and CWDTray Aspirator LTSeCore GSSPSeCore SBTAllSet Gold SSP DNA Wipe TestAllSet Gold SSP High ResolutionAllSet Gold SSP Low ResolutionMicro SSP 96-well transfer deviceMicro SSP Allele Specific TraysMicro SSP AmbistripsMicro SSP Ancillary ProductsMicro SSP Bulk Primer SetsMicro SSP Generic TraysMicro SSP High Resolution TraysTerasaki HLA Tissue Typing TraysTerasaki Supplement HLA Tissue Typing TraysTerasaki Cover SlidesTerasaki TraysB27 Monoclonal AntibodyBulk Monoclonal AntibodiesCytotoxic ControlsDynabeadsFluoroBeads Isolation ReagentsFluoroQuench Staining/Quenching ReagentGoat IgG Anti-Human KappaHeavy Mineral OilLympho-KwikPooled Human SerumRabbit ComplementHigh Fidelity DNA PolymeraseHot Start DNA PolymeraseTaq DNA PolymeraseHot-Start and Standard PCR MastermixesPfu and high-fidelity PCR mastermixes
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: May 24th, 2018
This privacy policy sets out how VH Bio Ltd uses and protects any information that you give VH Bio Ltd when you use this website.
VH Bio Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
VH Bio Ltd may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 24/05/2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name and job title
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@vhbio.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the General Data Protection Regulations. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to VH Bio Ltd, Unit 11B Station Approach, Team Valley Trading Estate, Gateshead, NE11 0ZF.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Find Products
We work with a range of suppliers with novel and innovative products
sourced from our global partners.
Find Products
Browser Warning
VHBio is not supported on Internet Explorer and will not provide you with the best
experience. Please consider switching to a compatible browser such as Microsoft Edge, Google Chrome or Firefox.
